<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brad Leege</title>
    <description>Personal Web site of Brad Leege</description>
    <link>www.leege.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="www.leege.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 20:09:46 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 20:09:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>FCFinder V2 - Football (Soccer), GraphQL, and SwiftUI Pandemic Adventures</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;em&gt;FCFinder V2 is an application for displaying the locations of football clubs by league and by year.&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;background&quot;&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A combination of events earlier this year led me to my most recent personal side project, FC Finder V2.  Specificaly, I’d been wanting to explore &lt;a href=&quot;https://graphql.org&quot;&gt;GraphQL&lt;/a&gt; as well as start learning &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/swiftui/&quot;&gt;SwiftUI&lt;/a&gt;, especailly after Apple announced it’s second rev at WWDC in June.  My problem was that I couldn’t decide on a good way to do so until the timely combination of the COVID-19 pandemic and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.mapbox.com/deprecating-studio-classic-styles-d8892ac38cb4&quot;&gt;deprecation of Mapbox Classic Map Styles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European and North American pandemic shutdowns in the spring resulted in the last 2 months of the traditional season of football leagues in Europe being put on hold until pandemic could be managed in each country (except for the USA 🤦‍♂️).  Seasons traditionally start in August and end in May so that meant in order to begin the new 2020-2021 season many leagues had to first complete their 2019-2020 seasons.  The result was that there was a glut of football being broadcast in the USA over the summer as different countries’ leagues returned to finish their seasons and I became curious to learn more about these leagues and their clubs, many of which I’d never watched before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d built a &lt;a href=&quot;/2012/12/08/this-is-my-latest-personal-project-called-fc.html&quot;&gt;Web application called FC Finder&lt;/a&gt; back in 2012 that mapped football leagues’ clubs and displayed the current favorite beers of the local supporters using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://untappd.com/api/docs&quot;&gt;Untappd API&lt;/a&gt;.  There were a couple of major problems with repurposing this Web app though, namely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The hardcoded club rosters had become out of date due to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Promotion_and_relegation&quot;&gt;relegation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The map stopped displaying due to the End of Life of Mapbox Classic Map Styles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From this FCFinder V2 was born.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;extensible-data-model-served-by-graphql&quot;&gt;Extensible Data Model Served By GraphQL&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extensibility was the primary feature for the new system.  While the original had leagues and their clubs hardcoded client side, the new system needed to be able to support different countries, different league tiers, and different seasons.  To solve this problem I created a data model containing Clubs, Leagues, and Countries that were tied together via a lookup table called ClubsToLeagues running in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.postgresql.org&quot;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had never worked with GraphQL before so I was eager to find out for myself how it all operated and if it lived up to the hype.  I decided that I wanted to write the server application in &lt;a href=&quot;https://kotlinlang.org&quot;&gt;Kotlin&lt;/a&gt; and host it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heroku.com&quot;&gt;Heroku&lt;/a&gt;.  I was really pleased to find and make use of &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ExpediaGroup/graphql-kotlin&quot;&gt;Expedia’s GraphQL-Kotlin&lt;/a&gt; library for this project.  I found the library and examples to be exactly what I needed to not only wrap my head around how GraphQL worked but also how to then build out what I needed.  It integrated easily with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sparkjava.com&quot;&gt;Spark Java Web framework&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JetBrains/Exposed&quot;&gt;JetBrain’s Exposed ORM&lt;/a&gt; to provide a clean multi-tiered architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/20201129/graphql-architecture.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite learnings about GraphQL is that generates API schema when run.  This is immensely helpful for confirming what has been built while in active development.  It’s also incredibly helpful for clients that will make use of the API.  That said, I found that it’s &lt;em&gt;absolutely imperative&lt;/em&gt; to use the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/graphql/graphql-playground&quot;&gt;GraphQL Playground&lt;/a&gt; app to work with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to all of this open source software and community I was able to learn GraphQL and to build a functional GraphQL server that powers the client application.  To pay it forward I’ve also made my server code available on GitHub for others to see and hopefully learn from.  It’s available at:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bleege/FCFinderV2&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bleege/FCFinderV2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;swiftui-client&quot;&gt;SwiftUI Client&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the surface SwiftUI’s opinionated design, namely a stateless declaritive UI that reflects a dynamic data model, makes a lot of sense.  In essence it’s a classic &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Model–view–viewmodel&quot;&gt;MVVM design pattern&lt;/a&gt;.  In practice though I found it to be more of a lift to wrap my head around it than I originally anticipated.  Specifically, the interplay of the new annotations &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@ObservedObject&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@Published&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@State&lt;/code&gt; and their bindings to the View’s objects.  The biggest issue was with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/swiftui/picker&quot;&gt;Picker&lt;/a&gt; and getting it to track selections.  I eventually was able to settle on a solution by specifying a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.tag()&lt;/code&gt; for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/swiftui/text&quot;&gt;Text&lt;/a&gt; in each Picker and binding it the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@Published&lt;/code&gt; var in the ViewModel.  It makes sense now that it has been built but building it initially took more thought than I originally had expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/20201129/selection-ux.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I was able to nail down the data state binding issue I found the rest of the build out to be quite smooth.  The &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/combine&quot;&gt;Combine Framework&lt;/a&gt; is a very welcome shift in the Apple ecosystem to provide out of the box support for reactive applications.  I’m a big fan of &lt;a href=&quot;http://reactivex.io&quot;&gt;Rx&lt;/a&gt; so it’s nice to no longer have to bundle 3rd party libraries to build a reactive application.  Combine does a good job of providing a lot of the necessary glue that binds SwiftUI’s View and Model so this whole system works.  That said I did find that just like RxSwift really shines when paired with RxCocoa, Combine is very much missing that Widget wrapper layer.  Thankfully the &lt;a href=&quot;https://combine.community&quot;&gt;Combine Community&lt;/a&gt; is actively building out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/CombineCommunity/CombineCocoa&quot;&gt;CombineCocoa&lt;/a&gt; library to fill this gap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also made the source code for the client available on GitHub.  Please feel free to explore it at:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bleege/FCFinderV2App&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bleege/FCFinderV2App&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thoughts&quot;&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really enjoyed this project (not to mention definitely filled some of the time gap caused by the pandemic lockdown) and getting to wrap my head around both of these relatively new technologies.  I can see the merits of GraphQL, but like anything it’s not a one size fits all tool.  I think it’s major use case is going to be as an abstraction layer for existing data services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for SwiftUI, I think it’s a major step in the right direction for Apple.  That said it still feels a bit under baked (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/mapkit/map&quot;&gt;MapKit’s Map&lt;/a&gt;).  It’s also held back by being an iOS 13+ technology (and iOS 14+ only in cases like MapKit).  Thankfully iOS 12 usage numbers should finally start to dry up in many mainstream apps which will allow SwiftUI and Combine to start being used more.  I think Combine is actually going to lead when it comes to adoption as it’s easier to refactor existing app plumbing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/20201129/london-club-map.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;next-steps&quot;&gt;Next Steps&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next on the TODO list to keep adding countries, leagues, and seasons to the data model.  I really love seeing the clubs mapped out, especially Tier 1 vs Tier 2 in the same country, as I find it an interesting way to learn about likely rivalries (derbys) between clubs as well as get a feel for some of the socio-economic situations for different clubs and their supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also considering adding macOS support to the client.  One of the promises of SwiftUI is that it’s relatively easy to be able to build apps that work well across all of Apple’s hardware and OS environments.  I’d like to get a feel for just how true that is.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2020/11/29/fcfinderv2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2020/11/29/fcfinderv2.html</guid>
        
        <category>iOS</category>
        
        <category>GraphQL</category>
        
        <category>Heroku</category>
        
        <category>Kotlin</category>
        
        <category>SwiftUI</category>
        
        <category>Swift</category>
        
        <category>PostgreSQL</category>
        
        <category>Projects</category>
        
        
        <category>Projects</category>
        
        <category>SwiftUI</category>
        
        <category>GraphQL</category>
        
        <category>Kotlin</category>
        
        <category>iOS</category>
        
        <category>PostgreSQL</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UIKonf 2020 Goes Remote</title>
        <description>&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The organizers of &lt;a href=&quot;https://uikonf.com&quot;&gt;UIKonf&lt;/a&gt; just announced that this year’s conference will be remote only due to COVID-19 pandemic.  I’m really glad that they did this to help in the fight against this disease while still allowing the conference to continue.  UIKonf has been my favorite tech conference due to it’s forward thinking and social nature and this year is shaping up to be no different.  The best part is now everyone can experience this for themselves for just € 100.
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Switching formats is not an easy nor inexpensive task, especially when it occurs a little over a month from dates of the conference (May 17 to May 19).  As such it’s very important to the iOS Community, and me personally, that we help the organizers out as best we can so that not only can UIKonf happen in 2020 but that it’s also able to survive for future years.  I’ve been lucky enough to get to know the organizers over the past few years personally and I can understand the pressure they’re under.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s some options for how you can help:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Buy a &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/uikonf/uikonf-2020&quot;&gt;Remote Ticket&lt;/a&gt; for € 100&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make a &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/uikonf/uikonf-2020/with/u-uwf4mk1cc&quot;&gt;Support Donation&lt;/a&gt; for € 100&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you’ve previously bought a Regular Ticket for € 559 tell the organizers that you’d like to donate the € 459 conversion to Remote Ticket rebate that they’re offering.  It’s what I’ve done already and would happily do again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2020/04/04/uikonf-remote.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2020/04/04/uikonf-remote.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>berlin</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>conferences</category>
        
        <category>covid-19</category>
        
        <category>equality</category>
        
        <category>europe</category>
        
        <category>germany</category>
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>livestream</category>
        
        <category>mobile</category>
        
        <category>pandemic</category>
        
        <category>people</category>
        
        <category>remote</category>
        
        <category>swift</category>
        
        <category>uikonf</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        
        <category>Conferences</category>
        
        <category>Community</category>
        
        <category>Berlin</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UIKonf 2019 Review</title>
        <description>&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was my second time attending &lt;a href=&quot;http://uikonf.com&quot;&gt;UIKonf&lt;/a&gt; in Berlin and it more than lived up to my fondest &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/05/24/uikonf.html&quot;&gt;memories from UIKonf 2018&lt;/a&gt;.  I was pleasantly surprised by to find the so many people that I’d met and interacted with the previous year were back again and that they all remembered me!  It was truly being back amongst friends… even after a year’s time and 4400 miles travelled.
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As UIKonf is well known for, the quality and range of topics again this year was no different.  Traditionally the conference organizers utilize an anonymous Call For Proposal process to select the talks, but this year decided to have an &lt;a href=&quot;http://uikonf.com/2019/01/29/all-female-speaker-lineup.html&quot;&gt;“all-female speaker line up on stage”&lt;/a&gt;.  While this caused some consternation when it was announced, by far the feedback that I heard while there and my own personal experience being there was very positive.  &lt;strong&gt;UIKonf was still UIKonf.&lt;/strong&gt;  I think this was a great experiment and more importantly sets the bar much higher for other tech conferences in having more women as featured speakers going forward.  There should be no more excuses.  For more details about the reasoning behind this check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hackingwithswift.com/articles/174/uikonf-goes-all-female-for-2019-speakers&quot;&gt;Hacking with Swift’s interview with conference organizer Sabine Geithner&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m already looking forward to attending again next year, but until then please enjoy a few of my favorite presentations from this year:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;shannon-hughes---detangling-gesture-recognizers&quot;&gt;Shannon Hughes - Detangling Gesture Recognizers&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/yw1AVD_0_w8&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;julie-yaunches---consistency-principle&quot;&gt;Julie Yaunches - Consistency Principle&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/3HoCsq6ijWY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sally-shepard---swift-to-hack-hardware&quot;&gt;Sally Shepard - Swift to Hack Hardware&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/_LlNHWl7fqY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;füsun-wehrmann---from-heroic-leaders-to-high-performing-teams&quot;&gt;Füsun Wehrmann - From Heroic Leaders To High Performing Teams&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/2KsbaibzB04&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ellen-shapiro---kotlinnative&quot;&gt;Ellen Shapiro - Kotlin/Native&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/dMm6zyW2i9I&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;kate-castellano---what-to-expect-when-you-are-templating-clues-approach-to-backend-driven-uis&quot;&gt;Kate Castellano - What to expect when you are templating? Clue’s approach to Backend Driven UIs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/_Dom_Fn87C0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more great talks please explore the full &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLdr22uU_wISr-FYeKblv3LMe_kHFzRFBw&quot;&gt;UIKonf 2019 Session Playlist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2019/06/23/unikonf.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2019/06/23/unikonf.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>berlin</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>conferences</category>
        
        <category>diversity</category>
        
        <category>equality</category>
        
        <category>europe</category>
        
        <category>germany</category>
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>kotlin</category>
        
        <category>mobile</category>
        
        <category>people</category>
        
        <category>swift</category>
        
        <category>uikonf</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        
        <category>Conferences</category>
        
        <category>Community</category>
        
        <category>Berlin</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beautiful night along the Spree in Berlin</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2019/05/31/berlin-spree-photo.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2019/05/31/berlin-spree-photo.html</guid>
        
        <category>berlin</category>
        
        <category>europe</category>
        
        <category>germany</category>
        
        <category>photos</category>
        
        <category>spree</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        
        <category>Berlin</category>
        
        <category>Travel</category>
        
        <category>Photos</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DotSwift 2019 Review</title>
        <description>&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I attended the &lt;a href=&quot;https://2019.dotswift.io/&quot;&gt;DotSwift conference&lt;/a&gt; in Paris, France the last week of January.  It’s an afternoon of a series of 18 minute talks and 5 “lightning talks” that last 4 minutes all on topics related to Swift software development.  This conference brings together people from across Europe and North America and emphasizes presence / social interaction.  In fact one of my favorite things about the conferece was it’s “No Wifi” policy.  This encouraged attendees and presenters to talk with each other during breaks as well as enable attendees to give their full attention to the presentations.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of my favorite presentations from the conference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;daniel-jalkut---just-enough-objective-c&quot;&gt;Daniel Jalkut - Just Enough Objective-C&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discusses how even “Pure Swift” apps live in a world of Objective-C code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/eSxXmnmjYZk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;mark-dalrymple---wht-is-tht&quot;&gt;Mark Dalrymple - Wh@t is th@t?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A deep dive into what annotations are, how they work, and most interestly how to find them in the iOS SDK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/MPkMf7Pbp5c&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;janina-kutyn---catransform3d-you-dont-need-to-know-them&quot;&gt;Janina Kutyn - CATransform3D: You don’t need to know them&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fascinating technical details about the math that powers Apple’s Core Animation APIs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vZq09zB0sfU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;soroush-khanlou---from-problem-to-solution&quot;&gt;Soroush Khanlou - From Problem to Solution&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A guide on how simplied solutions reveal themselves via iteration and abstraction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3G_ffcgRLMw&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the conference make sure to checkout the conference &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dotconferences.com/conference/dotswift-2019&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/97226415@N08/sets/72157676085258497/&quot;&gt;photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2019/02/03/dotswift.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2019/02/03/dotswift.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>conferences</category>
        
        <category>dotswift</category>
        
        <category>europe</category>
        
        <category>france</category>
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>mobile</category>
        
        <category>paris</category>
        
        <category>people</category>
        
        <category>swift</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        
        <category>Conferences</category>
        
        <category>Community</category>
        
        <category>Paris</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eifel Tower At Night</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2019/01/27/paris-eifel-tower-at-night.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2019/01/27/paris-eifel-tower-at-night.html</guid>
        
        <category>paris</category>
        
        <category>europe</category>
        
        <category>france</category>
        
        <category>photos</category>
        
        <category>eifel-tower</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        
        <category>Paris</category>
        
        <category>Travel</category>
        
        <category>Photos</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twice Is Nice! Simple Featured Again On Apple App Store</title>
        <description>&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week Apple is (again!) featuring the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/simple-better-banking/id479317486?mt=8&quot;&gt;Simple Finance iOS app&lt;/a&gt; as the top budgeting app for college students. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;College is an exciting time that often also comes with many new responsiblities, not the least of which is learning how to manage money.  This can be a scary and difficult life skill to learn, especially with so many other things happening simulataneously.  I’m really excited to see our team’s work promoted as a tool for helping college students learn these skills in a safe, straightforward, and simple way.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2018/08/22/simple-college-budgeting-app-store-featured.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2018/08/22/simple-college-budgeting-app-store-featured.html</guid>
        
        <category>apps</category>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>appstore</category>
        
        <category>budget</category>
        
        <category>highered</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>product</category>
        
        <category>simple-finance</category>
        
        
        <category>App Store</category>
        
        <category>Simple</category>
        
        <category>Featured</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Simple Featured On Apple App Store</title>
        <description>&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/simple-better-banking/id479317486?mt=8&quot;&gt;Simple Finance iOS app&lt;/a&gt; was featured by Apple on the App Store under the category of “Best New Updates”. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire team at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simple.com&quot;&gt;Simple&lt;/a&gt; has been heads down this year building and shipping new features for our customers.  It’s incredibly gratifying to be recognized for our work and are thankful for it.  You can check these features for yourself by &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/simple-better-banking/id479317486?mt=8&quot;&gt;downloading the app&lt;/a&gt; and by reading about them on the Simple blog:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simple.com/company/our-most-requested-feature-has-arrived&quot;&gt;Simple Expenses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simple.com/company/there-when-you-need-it-introducing-the-emergency-fund-goal&quot;&gt;Emergency Fund Goal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simple.com/company/goals-just-got-a-whole-lot-smarter&quot;&gt;Automated Goals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2018/08/14/simple-app-store-featured.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2018/08/14/simple-app-store-featured.html</guid>
        
        <category>apps</category>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>appstore</category>
        
        <category>best-new-updates</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>product</category>
        
        <category>simple-finance</category>
        
        <category>updates</category>
        
        
        <category>App Store</category>
        
        <category>Simple</category>
        
        <category>Featured</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tracking My Car's Mileage With Fuel App</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;tl;dr: I built (and open sourced) an iPhone X app to track my car’s fuel usage.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;background&quot;&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bought my current car in 2016 (Volkswagen Jetta  ❤️) and was interested in knowing how long (if at all) the advertised fuel efficicany of the car held up.  To do this I’ve been recording the mileage everytime I stop to refuel.  I have done this manually by recording the trip odometer, the amount of gas bought, what type of gas bought, etc and then entering it into a spreadsheet at home since I bought the car.  I’ve now been able to automate this process by creating an app for my personal iPhone X.
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;introducting-fuel&quot;&gt;Introducting Fuel&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuel is an app that allows me to record all the relevant fuel stop data while I’m at the gas station and then persist the data securely and privately in CloudKit.  This is such a time saver in addition to helping avoid forgetting to enter data at a later date.  It also lets me access these fuel stop records so I can track and compare the data over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/20180603/fuel-overview.png&quot; alt=&quot;Fuel Overview Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tech-used&quot;&gt;Tech Used&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really like to explore new tools, libraries, and frameworks when I’m building personal projects and this was project was no different.  This time out I got to work with &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ReactiveX/RxSwift&quot;&gt;RxSwift&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/cloudkit&quot;&gt;CloudKit&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Carthage/Carthage&quot;&gt;Carthage&lt;/a&gt; to name a few.  In addition to those tools for the app I also got to dive deeper on using mock objects in Swift to test architectural patterns as well the asychronous actions of RxSwift with &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/documentation/xctest/&quot;&gt;XCTest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/20180603/fuel-stop-detail.png&quot; alt=&quot;Fuel Overview Map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;source-code-available&quot;&gt;Source Code Available&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I’m handling distribution of the app to select devices via TestFlight and not publishing this app publically on the App Store, I am happy to make the source code available for others to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/bleege/Fuel&quot;&gt;https://github.com/bleege/Fuel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2018/06/03/fuel-app.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2018/06/03/fuel-app.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple-maps</category>
        
        <category>apps</category>
        
        <category>cars</category>
        
        <category>carthage</category>
        
        <category>cloudkit</category>
        
        <category>core-location</category>
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>location</category>
        
        <category>mobile</category>
        
        <category>opensource</category>
        
        <category>personal-projects</category>
        
        <category>privacy</category>
        
        <category>rxswift</category>
        
        <category>swift</category>
        
        <category>testflight</category>
        
        <category>xctest</category>
        
        
        <category>Projects</category>
        
        <category>Cars</category>
        
        <category>Mobile</category>
        
        <category>iOS</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UIKonf 2018 Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;tl;dr: A collection of my favorite presentations from UIKonf, an independent technical and community conference for iOS developers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--excerpt.start--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had the great pleasure to attend &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.uikonf.com&quot;&gt;UIKonf&lt;/a&gt; in Berlin, Germany last week.  It was a single track conference over two days that had a great balance of technical, business, and socially positive presentations.  I really enjoyed getting to meet and learn from some incredible people from around the world.  Here are some of my favorite presentations:
&lt;!--excerpt.end--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;kamilah-taylor---tired-of-the-state-of-online-conversations--lets-do-something-about-it-&quot;&gt;Kamilah Taylor - Tired of the state of online conversations? 🙈🙉🙊 Let’s do something about it 💪&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A fantastic look at how today’s social media platforms’ internal business measures of success encourage the polarization, misinformation, and distrust we’re seeing in society.  More importantly, what people are starting to do to fix these problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Nx0cKEQcbz4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;john-sundell---the-magic-of-ui-testing&quot;&gt;John Sundell - The Magic of UI Testing&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great advice on how to find the right balance between test coverage, utility, and speed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/YzuJoVnxJCw&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;carola-nitz---advanced-debugging-techniques&quot;&gt;Carola Nitz - Advanced Debugging Techniques&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A deep dive on some (not widely known) tools and techniques for finding and fixing issues with UIs and performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/578YdS2sNqk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;dave-delong---the-laws-of-magic&quot;&gt;Dave DeLong - The Laws of Magic&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A brand new talk from Dave where he discusses 3 “laws” for building engaging experiences and apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gx9ywSNm1jM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;janina-kutyn---improving-scrolling-performance-through-gpu-optimisation&quot;&gt;Janina Kutyn - Improving Scrolling Performance through GPU Optimisation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An introduction to how device CPU and GPU work together to produce smooth UIs and how you can improve their collaboration for your app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ypPX8CJmRIY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;vincent-garrigues---scaling-ios-a-story-of-technical-debt-and-how-to-get-through-it&quot;&gt;Vincent Garrigues - Scaling iOS, a story of technical debt, and how to get through it&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A story about the unitended consquences of rewriting the SoundCloud app, what the team learned from this experience, and how they used what they learned to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fmzA7cLyKv0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire set of conference presentations are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nx0cKEQcbz4&amp;amp;list=PLdr22uU_wISohI7PIhzq0gotGfKZl1lGo&quot;&gt;also available on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>www.leege.io/2018/05/24/uikonf.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.leege.io/2018/05/24/uikonf.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>berlin</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>conferences</category>
        
        <category>europe</category>
        
        <category>germany</category>
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>ios</category>
        
        <category>mobile</category>
        
        <category>people</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>uikonf</category>
        
        
        <category>Conferences</category>
        
        <category>Community</category>
        
        <category>Berlin</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
